All right so let's look at the counter argument to the idea that video games are bad or do have a negative
好吧，让我们来看看视频游戏不好或确实有负面观点的反驳论点
effect on young people.
对年轻人的影响。
So now the answer is No.
所以现在答案是否定的。
And this is our counter which means against or opposite argument argument.
这是我们的反驳，意思是反对或反对论点。
OK now we're going to use some of the expressions we've learned so look out for those.
好的，现在我们将使用我们学到的一些表达方式，因此请注意这些表达方式。
If that were true.
如果那是真的。
Remember the previous person said that there is an effect of being very impressionable and so kids will
记得前一个人说过，有一种非常易受影响的效果，所以孩子们会
learn that behavior.
学习这种行为。
If that were true little kids would be would be running around outside right now with knives and guns
如果那是真的，小孩子现在会拿着刀和枪在外面跑来跑去
because violent video games are everywhere.
因为暴力电子游戏无处不在。
OK.
好的。
Because anybody can play violent video games.
因为任何人都可以玩暴力视频游戏。
Many kids play them any way we know that.
许多孩子以我们知道的任何方式玩它们。
That's a fact.
这是事实。
If what you're saying were true then we would see violence all over the place.
如果你说的是真的，那么我们会看到到处都是暴力。
We would have little kids running around stabbing people and shooting people.
我们会让小孩子四处乱窜，刺伤人，射人。
That's the interesting point.
这就是有趣的地方。
Right.
正确的。
OK remember what we do here is we show either we ask the question why to show either why what you're
好的，记住我们在这里所做的是我们展示我们问这个问题为什么要展示你为什么
saying is not true because this is true or we're saying if what you're saying were true this thing should
说不是真的，因为这是真的，或者我们在说如果你说的是真的这件事应该
be true but it's not.
是真的，但事实并非如此。
In fact we don't see kids running around with knives and guns.
事实上，我们没有看到孩子们拿着刀和枪到处乱跑。
So that means what you're saying is probably not true.
所以这意味着你所说的可能不是真的。
OK.
好的。
Because violent video games are everywhere.
因为暴力视频游戏无处不在。
There's certainly no denying.
肯定是不可否认的。
Now remember this is the way that we can agree with another person's point and then change the focus.
现在记住这是我们可以同意另一个人的观点然后改变焦点的方式。
The point was.
重点是。
Isn't it true.
是不是真的。
Isn't it true that young people are more impressionable.
年轻人是不是更易受影响。
There's no denying.
无可否认。
Here we are.
我们到了。
There's no denying that young people are more impressionable than adults.
不可否认，年轻人比成年人更容易受到影响。
OK.
好的。
So I'm giving you that point.
所以我给你这一点。
That's true.
确实如此。
But they are also clearly capable of distinguishing real life from video games.
但它们也显然能够将现实生活与电子游戏区分开来。
So I'm saying yes they're impressionable but they can tell the difference to distinguish means to be
所以我说是的，他们是易受影响的，但他们可以区分不同的意思
able to tell the difference if you can distinguish between different types of coffee.
如果你能区分不同类型的咖啡，就能分辨出区别。
That means you can tell the difference.
这意味着你可以分辨出来。
All of this one is from Colombia and this one is from Africa for example.
所有这一个都来自哥伦比亚，这个来自非洲。
OK.
好的。
They're capable or able to distinguish real life from video games.
他们有能力或能够将现实生活与电子游戏区分开来。
The rules of the game are to shoot and kill the rules of the game or to shoot and kill.
游戏规则是射杀游戏规则或射杀。
If you do those things you win in real life.
如果你做了这些事情，你就会在现实生活中获胜。
If you do those things you lose lose maybe means you know go to jail or something.
如果你做了那些你失去的事情，你可能会失去可能意味着你知道要进监狱什么的。
Kids aren't stupid.
孩子不傻。
It's up to parents to teach kids what is right and wrong.
父母应该教孩子什么是对什么错。
So on this side it's saying hey what you're saying is not right because if what you're saying were true
所以在这一边，它说嘿，你说的不对，因为如果你说的是真的
you'd have kids running around with guns.
你会让孩子拿着枪到处乱跑。
In fact kids can tell the difference in a game.
事实上，孩子们可以在游戏中分辨出不同之处。
You have to kill in real life.
你必须在现实生活中杀人。
You can't do that in a game.
你不能在游戏中做到这一点。
Violence is good in real life.
暴力在现实生活中是好的。
It's not.
它不是。
It's up to parents to teach kids what is right and what is wrong.
父母应该教孩子什么是对的，什么是错的。
Kids aren't stupid.
孩子不傻。
They're able to tell the difference between this game and out there in real life.
他们能够分辨出这款游戏与现实生活中的区别。
The rules that you have to play to maybe succeed.
您必须遵守的规则才能成功。
OK.
好的。
So this is just a counter argument to the previous one and this could go back and forth.
所以这只是对前一个的反驳，这可能会来来回回。
We could do another one but notice we have used some of the expressions that we learned earlier on in
我们可以再做一个，但请注意我们使用了一些我们之前在
this lesson.
这节课。
Now I hope that you have a feeling for how debates go now and that you could if you had to then go on
现在我希望你对辩论现在的进展有感觉，如果你不得不继续的话，你可以
and support one side or the other and give more reasons why either violent video games are very negative
并支持一方或另一方，并给出更多理由说明暴力电子游戏为何非常消极
or why violent video games are no problem.
或者为什么暴力视频游戏没有问题。
Hopefully you could use some of the expressions we've learned to do that.
希望您可以使用我们学到的一些表达方式来做到这一点。
But I'm going to give you another topic to work on as an assignment and I want you to make sure to use
但我会给你另一个主题作为作业，我希望你确保使用
these expressions and use the things we learned in this lesson.
这些表达方式并使用我们在本课中学到的东西。
To do that.
要做到这一点。
Now to practice this what I'd like you to do is as usual record yourself actually doing both sides of
现在练习这个我想让你做的就是像往常一样记录你自己实际上做的两面
a debate.
一场辩论。
Both sides of the debate play devil's advocate with yourself.
辩论的双方都在自欺欺人。
Make sure to record it.
确保记录下来。
OK give as much detail as you can.
好的，尽可能多地提供细节。
Make analogies if you can to help clarify things to your audience which may be yourself and make sure
如果可以，请进行类比，以帮助向可能是您自己的听众澄清事情，并确保
to use the expressions that we learned in this lesson the debate topic is medical testing on animals
使用我们在本课中学到的表达方式，辩论主题是对动物的医学测试
is right or wrong.
是对还是错。
That means we should test medicine new medicines on animals like rats or we should not.
这意味着我们应该在老鼠等动物身上测试新药，或者我们不应该。
OK.
好的。
And there are a lot of different reasons why we should maybe and why we shouldn't try to explore those
有很多不同的原因为什么我们应该或者为什么我们不应该尝试探索这些
and explore also the expressions we learned.
并探索我们学到的表达方式。
So good luck with that and I will see you in the next video.
祝你好运，我会在下一个视频中见到你。